evolveterminal.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy Policy | Terminals by Evolve PR

##  Our privacy policy 

This document sets forth the privacy practices of Evolve PR Inc., Evolve Terminal and other affiliates and trademarks operated by Evolve PR Inc. ("Evolve PR Inc." or "we" or "us"), the Evolve Termina Apps and subsites [*.evolveterminal.com] (the "Site"), and the terms which govern the collection and use of information you provide to us whether via the Site or otherwise. By accessing or using the Site and/or providing any personal information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept these practices, you must not access or use the Site or provide us with your personal information. 

##  What Information Do We Collect? 

###  Personal Information 

In describing the information we collect, the term "personal information" refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, company name, phone number, email or postal address. In many cases we need this information to provide the products or services that you have requested. Unless necessary to provide our products and services, the amount of personal information that you choose to disclose to Evolve PR Inc. is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us. In order to process certain transactions, we may also need to collect payment information from you (e.g., credit card information) which will not be shared with anyone outside of Evolve PR Inc., its affiliates and the financial institutions and vendors used to process payments. We do not intentionally collect any sensitive information, such as information concerning race, religion, health, sexual orientation or political beliefs. Please do not send any sensitive personal information to us. 

###  Voluntary Information 

We receive and store any information you voluntarily communicate to us in connection with your use of our Site or which you may voluntarily communicate to us in any other fashion. You may choose not to provide certain information we request from you. However, if you so elect, we may not be able to provide our products and services, and you might not be able to access or take full advantage of the features and functionality of the Site. Once you initiate a voluntary transaction, we will ask you for certain information depending upon the nature of the transaction in question. For example: 

  * When you request to create an account, we ask for your name, email address and your location.
  * When you submit a request to receive our newsletter, we ask for your email address to deliver the newsletter.
  * When you have signed up and if there is an offer to send a welcome package, we may ask you for your phone number and mailing address
  * When you participate in social actions or discussions on the Site, any information posted in these areas of the Site becomes public information, and you should exercise care when disclosing personal information.

###  Cookies 

Certain types of information relating to you or arising from your use of the Site are automatically collected whenever you interact with the Site. A "cookie" is a small set of data that a website server may transmit to the internet browser of a person upon their initial visit to the website, which is updated with each return visit. Websites may use cookies for a number of different purposes, such as the storing of your personal information and browsing preferences so you do not have to reset or retype them at future visits. Most internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to disable acceptance of any cookies, or give you the option of accepting or rejecting any particular cookie. Please consult the "help" function in your browser if you want to find out how to accept, disable or selectively enable cookies. However, certain features of the Site may not work as intended if you decline to accept cookies. 

Like many websites, we use cookies, 0-byte GIF files, and log files, and we also obtain certain types of information whenever your internet browser accesses the Site. If you are not a registered user of the Site, our cookies do not contain any personal information about you. Today, we only use the information that we gather from the use of cookies to: 

  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using our Site.
  * Monitor and understand aggregate visitor usage patterns at the Site, as well as estimate and report our total visitor size and traffic at the Site.
  * Identify problems experienced by visitors as they use our Site and to conduct research and analysis to debug the content and services available at the Site.
  * Help us develop and improve our products, services and the design, layout and functionality of the Site.

Except as described in the foregoing, we do not currently use cookies for any other purposes. However, we reserve our rights to use cookies for additional purposes in the future. In the event we do change our policies regarding cookies in the future, we will post these changes in accordance with "Notification of Changes" section of this Policy. 

###  Information from Third Parties 

From time to time, we may also receive personal information about you from our business partners and affiliates and add it to our account information about you. 

##  How Do We Use The Information We Collect? 

###  General 

Until you initiate a voluntary transaction with us, we do not collect any personal information about you. The information we collect is generally used to: enable us to communicate with you; provide you with our products and services; process requests for information or otherwise as necessary to perform an agreement between you and Evolve PR Inc.; improve or add features, functionality and content to our Site; provide you with a more personalized experience at the Site; notify you about our new products, services and/or special offers or updates or improvements to our existing products and services. 

###  Email and other Correspondence 

We may send you email or other forms of correspondence that are intended to notify you of our new products, services, special offers or updates or improvements to our existing products and services. You have the right to "opt-out" and prohibit use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes. If you prefer not receive any such email correspondence or marketing information concerning our products and services, please click "unsubscribe" as instructed in any email from us. 

###  Disclosure to Third Parties 

The information that we collect from you via the Site and otherwise is an integral part of our business, and Evolve PR Inc. is not in the business of selling or renting your personal information to third parties. Evolve PR Inc. shares your personal information only with (i) its subsidiaries and affiliates around the world; and (ii) specified third parties under the conditions described below: 

> ####  International Disclosures 
> 
> Our products and services may be provided using affiliates and other resources located in various countries around the world, including those outside of the European Economic Area (EEA), that may not have laws providing specific protection for personal data or that do not have an adequate level of data protection. Personal information collected through this Site or otherwise by us may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which Evolve PR Inc., its affiliates or partners maintain offices, including the United States. By providing any personal information to us, you acknowledge that you are giving your consent to transfer your personal information to any Evolve PR Inc. affiliate or partner worldwide. 
> 
> ####  Partners and Third Parties 
> 
> Evolve PR Inc. may submit personal information to third parties as required or necessary to fulfill its services and/or performance of obligations. For example, Evolve PR Inc. may share personal information with its partners to enable a partner to provide support to a customer or where required to make a sale in a particular country. From time to time Evolve PR Inc. may employ or engage other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf. Examples include provision of accounting, legal and financial services, fulfilling orders, shipping packages, sending postal mail and email, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Such third parties may have access to your personal information if such is required in order to perform their service functions and may not use such information for any other purposes. Evolve PR Inc. maintains ownership and control of the information so used. 
> 
> ####  Sale of Business 
> 
> As we develop, expand and improve our lines of business, we might sell or purchase the assets of one or more of our own lines of business or those of third parties. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets, and accordingly we reserve our rights to sell or purchase customer information (including your personal information) in any such sale or business transaction. 
> 
> ####  Disclosure Required by Law 
> 
> Evolve PR Inc. may release your personal information if it believes such release is necessary to comply with law. 
> 
> ####  Disclosure With Your Consent 
> 
> Other than as described in the foregoing, you will receive prior notice from us in the event we propose to share your personal information with third parties, and you will have a reasonable opportunity to elect not to share the information. 

###  "Opt Out" and Complaint Procedures 

In addition to the options made available to you when we collect information (if any), you may elect to "opt out" of having your personal information shared with third parties (except for uses specifically requested by you and necessary business uses). You must submit a request (by mail, email, or telephone) to us in one of the following ways:

  * By Email Email address: terminal@evolve-pr.com

We will update the specific records related to your request as promptly as practical. Note, however, that you may receive additional communications after you submit your request while we process the request. Additionally, your information may exist in multiple lists within Evolve PR Inc., and our technology limits the processing of opt-out requests to the specific list source. 

##  Correcting Your Information, Inquires and Complaints 

We want any information you provide to be correct so you have the ability to change the information we have about you. You may object to the collection, transfer, storage and processing of your information at any time. In such a case, you may not be able to engage in an activity on the Site or Evolve PR Inc. may not be able to provide its products and services to you. You also may object to the use of your personal information for marketing purposes at any time without giving reasons via email at terminal@evolve-pr.com. If you wish to correct your information, or have any related questions or complaints, please contact us at terminal@evolve-pr.com. We reserve the right to reject or remove any information or content posted on our Site at our sole discretion. 

##  Security 

Our Site has commercially reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, you should keep in mind that this Site is run on software, hardware, and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance, experience problems or breaches of security. 

##  What About Links to Other Websites? 

This Site contains links to other websites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. For your own protection, you should review the policies upon visiting these other sites to make sure they meet your expectations of privacy. 

##  About Children's Privacy 

Our website is intended for a general audience and is not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

##  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or provide you with notice by other methods, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed. It is your responsibility to check back to this page occasionally to see these changes. 

This Privacy Policy was last amended on 14 May 2015.
